Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/marwan-ashraf- (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Team Leadership Teamwork Negotiation

Certifications

Python Data Structures

Database Fundamentals

Marwan Ashraf

Senior Risk Data Analyst at Tabby-UAE Cairo, Egypt

Summary

An experienced data analyst with Engineering background who worked in numerous fields like Fintech, financial services, retail, BNPL, Credit risk, customer experience and more.

With a strong and established knowledge in Data analysis and Business Intelligence, and a wide domain of knowledge and practical experience in statistics, and an experience in machine learning, probability and A/B testing

A 4+ years of hands-on experience in python, pysaprk, SQL, Tableau, PowerBI and more.

Experience

Tabby

1 year 9 months

Senior Risk Analyst August 2024 - Present (5 months) Cairo, Egypt

Risk Analyst

April 2023 - August 2024 (1 year 5 months)

Cairo, Egypt

Cassbana

Data Analyst

April 2022 - April 2023 (1 year 1 month)

Cairo, Egypt

Raya Holding for Financial Investments Data Scientist January 2021 - March 2022 (1 year 3 months) Cairo, Egypt

Education

Faculty of Engineering, Alexandria University, Egypt Student, Electrical, Electronics and Communications Engineering · (2015 - 2020)

Udacity

Nanodegree Program, Advanced Data Analysis · (2020)